Guide to the Judith Rosen Collection ARS.0032
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Women Orchestra Conductors, First National Congress on Women in Music, 1981-11-11; 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
  Following digitization, this item was found to be a duplicate of "Women Composers of Electronic Music, First National Congress on Women in Music".
- National Congress on Women in Music. Keynote Address, Susan McClary. Does Gender Matter: Theorizing Music by Women, 1997-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
- National Congress on Women in Music. Judith Tick, The Life of Ruth Crawford Seeger, 1997-05; 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
- Keynote Address - Elizabeth Wood. John Gillespie and Women Composers of Pianoforte music in 19th c. America [National Congress on Women in Music?], 1983-05-06; 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
- Charles Wuorinen. Genesis; Missa Brevis, 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
- Charles Wuorinen. The Magic Art, Act II, Scenes 2 and 3; Five Concerto for Amplified Cello and Orchestra, 1 audiocassette (Audio 7)
- [unidentified, numbered 1 and 2], 2 DATs (Audio 7)